{
    "subject": "resource/Adrian_P\u0103unescu",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Cop\u0103ceni,_S\u00eengerei",
    "human_readable": "Adrian P\u0103unescu was born in Cop\u0103ceni, S\u00eengerei.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9355519413948059,
            "question": "Where was Adrian P\u0103unescu born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7839949727058411,
            "question": "What was the name of Adrian P\u0103unescu's father?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7434509992599487,
            "question": "What is Adrian P\u0103unescu known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6768378019332886,
            "question": "What type of work did Adrian P\u0103unescu's father do?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5988185405731201,
            "question": "In what village did Adrian P\u0103unescu spend his childhood?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5355897545814514,
            "question": "Who was a major influence on Adrian P\u0103unescu's writing style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4962395429611206,
            "question": "Did Adrian P\u0103unescu study literature or another field?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.46027693152427673,
            "question": "What awards has Adrian P\u0103unescu received for his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3796573579311371,
            "question": "What is one famous poem written by Adrian P\u0103unescu?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35409048199653625,
            "question": "What year did Adrian P\u0103unescu publish his first collection of poems?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Adrian P\u0103unescu was born in Cop\u0103ceni, S\u00eengerei.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4159_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is one famous poem written by Adrian P\u0103unescu?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4159_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards has Adrian P\u0103unescu received for his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4159_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Adrian P\u0103unescu study literature or another field?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4159_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4159_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of whether the information in the documents supports the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that all the documents contain statements about Adrian P\u0103unescu's birthplace, and they consistently mention Cop\u0103ceni, S\u00eengerei as his place of birth."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe context information explicitly states, \"On July 20, 1943, in Cop\u0103ceni, S\u00eengerei district, Republic of Moldova, the great Adrian P\u0103unescu was born,\" which supports the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}